gtabase.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy & Cookies - GTABase.com

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### Privacy Policy

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect and how we safeguard your information.

  * **Log Files**  
Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers.  
 
  * **Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.  
 
  * **Cookies**  
This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.

###   
Cookie Policy

Below you can read about how cookies are used by this site. If you continue to use this site, you are consenting to our use of cookies.

**What Are Cookies**  
A cookie is a small piece of text sent to your browser by a website you visit. It helps the website to remember your settings preferences, to register and keep you logged in to our forums, to make the ads you see more relevant to you, to count how many visitors we receive to a page, etc. That can make your next visit easier and the site more useful to you. Cookies play an important role. Without them, using the web would be a much more frustrating experience.

**Our Cookie Usage**  
This site uses cookies for a variety of reasons, detailed below:

  * **Analytics.**  
We use analytics scripts to collect non-personally identifiable information regarding our website’s visitors. This helps us determine and analyze data regarding our site’s traffic and usage, and improve our website to serve our visitors better. We only use this information for analysis.  
For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the [official Google Analytics page](https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies).  
 
  * **Advertising cookies (possibly third-party).**  
The Google AdSense service we use to serve advertising uses a DoubleClick cookie to serve more relevant ads across the web and limit the number of times that a given ad is shown to you.  
For more information on Google AdSense see the [official Google AdSense privacy FAQ](http://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/ads/).  
 
  * **Other third-party cookies (like Facebook or Twitter sharing).**  
We use social media buttons and plugins on this site that allow you to connect with your social network in various ways. For these to work, social media sites (Facebook, Twitter) will set cookies through our site. These cookies will generally be set by the third-party independently, so this site will have no ability to access them.

**Removing/Disabling Cookies**

We do not use cookies to collect any personally identifiable information about you, but if you wish to restrict or block the cookies on our site, or any other website, you can do so through your browser settings.

Here is a list of guides on how to do this for popular browser software:

Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or Cookie Policy, please [contact us](https://www.gtabase.com/contact/).
